let questions = [
  {
      numb: 1,
      question: "Which HTML tag is used to create a form?",
      answer: "form",
      options: [
        "input",
        "form",
        "textarea",
        "button"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 2,
      question: "How do you define an input field in an HTML form?",
      answer: "input",
      options: [
        "field",
        "textbox",
        "text",
        "input"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 3,
      question: "What attribute of the input tag specifies the type of input?",
      answer: "type",
      options: [
          "value",
          "type",
          "name",
          "placeholder"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 4,
      question: "Which HTML tag is used to create a table?",
      answer: "table",
      options: [
        "tr",
        "td",
        "table",
        "thead"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 5,
      question: "How do you define a row in an HTML table?",
      answer: "tr",
      options: [
        "td",
        "th",
        "table",
        "tr"
      ]
    },
  {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Which tag is used to create a table header cell?",
      answer: "th",
      options: [
        "td",
        "th",
        "tr",
        "table"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 7,
      question: "What does the ul tag represent in HTML?",
      answer: "an unordered list",
      options: [
          "an ordered list",
          "a list item",
          "an unordered list",
          "a definition list"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 8,
      question: "How do you create a list item in an HTML list?",
      answer: "li",
      options: [
        "li",
        "list",
        "item",
        "ul"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 9,
      question: "What is the purpose of the h1 tag in HTML?",
      answer: "It defines the largest heading.",
      options: [
          "It defines a paragraph.",
          "It defines a section.",
          "It defines the largest heading.",
          "It defines a footer."
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 10,
      question: "Which HTML tag is self-closing?",
      answer: "img",
      options: [
          "div",
          "span",
          "img",
          "a"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 11,
      question: "What is the purpose of the form element in HTML?",
      answer: "It is used to collect user input.",
      options: [
          "It is used to create a table.",
          "It is used to link external resources.",
          "It is used to collect user input.",
          "It is used to define a list."
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 12,
      question: "Which HTML tag is used to define a block of text in a form that can be edited and stetched?",
      answer: "textarea",
      options: [
          "input",
          "textarea",
          "button",
          "select"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 13,
      question: "How do you specify a cell in a table body?",
      answer: "td",
      options: [
          "cell",
          "td",
          "tr",
          "th"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 14,
      question: "What HTML tag would you use to create a dropdown list?",
      answer: "select",
      options: [
          "dropdown",
          "select",
          "input",
          "option"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 15,
      question: "Which tag is used to create the body of a table? ",
      answer: "tbody",
      options: [
          "body",
          "tbody",
          "header",
          "tr"
      ]
  }
];
